Contact

nikhilkumar3121996@gmail.com Mobile no: 9307388414 www.linkedin.com/in/nikhil-kumarb1025b151

Top Skills

Microsoft PowerPoint ·
Microsoft Excel · Microsoft Word
Management Administration
HR Recruitment, Operations.

Accomplishments

2 Certifications

Won First Price Final Year Project B.tech State Level

Education

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Marketing and HR (IMED PUNE) (2019 – 2021) 89.4%.

B-Tech Electrical Engineering (MIT Moradabad) (2014-2018) 67.6%

Senior Secondary (XII) Science Moradabad School (CBSE Board) 2014 55.4%

Higher Secondary (X) Agra School CBSE Board 2011 66.7%

Extracurricular Activities

Volunteer of Entrepreneurship Cell

Participating Sports events Like Cricket etc.

Language: English, Hindi

Nikhil Kumar

I help companies to increase Growth & Identify best talent with my HR skill. Meerut, Uttar Pradesh, India

Summary

I have good business communication skills and good knowledge of Microsoft analytical tools. I have experience of recruitment and Training. I will help to generate business and identify potential Talents for the Organisation which is very important to your business success with my HR skills. I am a result-oriented HR who has relevant skills to identify insights. I will help to strengthen their company position. I help Organisations to identify potential threats & opportunities.

Experience

Management Intern Wayam Bharat Bangalore (6 Months)

Handling Recruitment of IT & Non-IT profiles and, Identifying Potential Candidates, HR Operations, Performance Management.

Research Intern · IRJI.IN Pune

June 2020 - September 2020 (4 months) -

Research Impact of AI on different Research based Consulting companies and different Collect Data & understand Research about Impact of AI on functional areas of Business processes.

Social Media Marketing Intern · the Contrast Mumbai

May 2020 - June 2020 (2 months)

I worked for a month an organization in digital marketing filed as a social LinkedIn platform on the different methods

Electrical Engineering Intern Northern Railway

June 2017-july 2017 (2 Months)

Worked in Railways Traction system OHE systems Learn Monitors Different Parameters on Substation Power System.

Projects

ic

- Personal Finance Management of Salaried Class Finance Project
- Study and Evaluation Performance Management HR Project
- Final Year Project: Impact of AI on Business Consulting Services.